I don't want nobody to get killed
I come and get you, I'm always ready to fight
So don't take all of the blame where all is spread
Oh, I don't take all of the blame, you always do
There will always be something you cannot control
We will overcome, your salvation has begun
No sun, no light, such a mess, I'm over
Don't kill your walls, you make me realize who I need
I'll be there, hold on, the changes temp house
So where are you now?
I'll reach you, my top, the shadows of the earth
Illusions are born
The golden end is still wrong, but I know it is a pain
That makes us a human after all
Toin' and see me, you follow the good show
About your precious words
This car may respond to your call
It's the four horsemen of John, get out of here!
Shit, we're dead!
Let the place go!
Help me!
My sword
We're saved
Maybe we'll get the same kind of protection they got in Osaka now
They think we've saved them
What idiotic creatures
We're just keeping our livestock fresh
Protecting our property
Right?
Well, it took a hell of a lot of strength to pull off that stunt
Word has it that you became a vampire by drinking the blood of the third progenitor, Queen Cruel Tepish herself
Tell me, are the rumors true?
Regardless of his background, he took the monster down before we could land any blows ourselves
Greedy bastard probably wants credit for the kill
You can have the body if you want it
Credit means nothing to me
From now on, this district will be governed by the vampires
We can guarantee your safety
In exchange for our protection, all we ask is that you donate blood so we may continue to keep you safe from harm
Um, hello
I would have died if you hadn't stopped that monster
I'm so grateful to be alive
Let me show my gratitude by offering my blood
Please drink until you're satisfied
A memory surfaces
They only look after us because we're their food
Listen to me, Mika
We've got to start a full-blown revolution
Otherwise, we're going to be livestock forever
Jeez, you always want to do stuff that'll get us in trouble
We're only in trouble if it doesn't work
There's no way we could beat the vampires in a frontal assault
Outsmarting them is the only way to go
I actually have an escape plan already
We can run away from the vampires together
You can leave everything up to me
I had so much hope in the time before my humanity ended
But then, it was because of this foolish hope that everything fell apart
Just go, you idiot!
No!
I'm... happy
I can leave this world at peace
Knowing you've escaped
What the hell happened here?
Lord Ferret appears to be injured
How dare one of these filthy humans lay a hand on a noble?
Hold it right there!
I've taken a particular interest in the blonde one
Anything you wish, my queen
He's losing a lot of blood
So I see
At this rate, he won't last much longer
I wonder how these children managed to catch you by surprise
Lord Ferret Bathory
Dear me
What a treat it is to be visited by our beloved queen, cruel Tepish herself
It's been far too long
You look ravishing as always
Why, thank you
And your grin is as smug and nauseating as I recall
How cruel
Here I am with a gunshot wound to my head
Yet I still manage a smile on my face because of my love for you
Really?
I think the only thing that you truly love about me is my power
You know my heart too well
You were attacked and injured by human children?
You were seventh progenitor for crying out loud
Wait, is this a joke?
I'm afraid it's not
I see, I didn't think you were that funny, Ferret
But now one of my seraphs has escaped
And the other one is dying, barely clinging to life
If you have any explanation for your actions, now would be the time for you to start
Ah, but you have plenty of explaining to do yourself, don't you, my queen?
You've been fiddling with the curse of the seraphs and that's against the law
If the progenitor council knew, they'd be furious
Hmm, what did you say?
You heard me
If I told the progenitor council
Oh, what's the matter, my queen?
Did I hit a nerve?
I'm sorry, I didn't catch what you were saying
Let's hear it one more time
You're so violent, cruel
Losing a limb hurts like hell
Even if I can reattach it and heal myself
You're lucky all I ripped off was your arm
This lover's spat has taken a turn
Alright, I am at your mercy
I promise not to meddle in your affairs any longer
I'm not an idiot
I know I couldn't survive crossing you
My lips are sealed when it comes to your precious seraphs
Good, they better be
Because if you pry into this matter again, you'll regret it
Don't worry, I value my life far too much to do that
But you haven't seen the last of me, cruel
After all, I do love you
Hey, human
Do you want to bleed out?
Because I can ensure that you survive all of this
I offer eternal life
I don't want it
I see, so you want to die like your friends
Unfortunately, you don't have much of a choice
Once you drink my blood, you'll become something far superior to a human
That was the moment
I lost my humanity
Hey, watch where you're going, you damn punk
Huh?
You trying to start a fight or something?
Wait, what are you talking about?
What the hell do you think you're doing?
Alright, you bastard
You asked for it
Whoa, you?
What happened to your face?
I walked into a telephone pole
A telephone pole?
That's right
A telephone pole with a nasty look and a really bad attitude
Sounds painful
The two of you are late
Whatever, we're here now
Looks like someone pummeled your face
Is another suspension in order?
It was an accident, not a fight
Well, alright, if you say so
Besides, we've got much bigger things on our plate today
Yeah, I'm so psyched
After all this waiting, we finally get to start training
To become members of the Moon Demon Company
You already know I don't need any training
Save us all some time and just put me in action
I'd be fine with that
But if you're not willing to put in the time to go through training
You're going to fight without gear or a uniform
I'm not killing vampires buck naked
Excuse me, everyone
I brought these two slowpokes with me, Lieutenant Colonel
Uh, sir?
Fine
Time to get started
The reason I'm making a rare appearance in class today
Is because we've got a couple of transfer students I want to introduce you to
You know, just for your information
The supervising teacher should probably be coming to class every day
Why don't you mind your own business?
So, anyway
As I was saying, these are the transfers
Yuichiro Hyakuya and Yuichi Saotome
Though it might be easier to remember them as the idiot and the wuss
You're calling me an idiot?
Well, it's the truth
Now go ahead and introduce yourselves
Why bother?
I don't care about any of the other people in this class
I'm not here to be liked or make friends
You weaklings can piss off and become vampire food for all I care
Whoa, what's gotten into you?
Let's make one thing clear
I don't know which one of you losers was the best in class till now
But you can kiss that goodbye
The strongest cursed gear is mine
I shouldn't even be wasting my time here
I deserve to be in the company
No, you deserve this
I don't know what you learned in that general ed class
But here we work together as a team
Thought you might have learned your place by now
Go on, take a seat in the back row
Stupid Gorin
Thinks he knows everything
Hey, move your feet
This is where the lieutenant colonel said I'm supposed to sit
You listening?
Time to get moving
Can't you see that I'm trying to sleep?
Back off
So we meet again, telephone pole
What are you doing here?
I could ask you the same question, you twerp
And what do you mean, telephone pole?
What's the story with those two?
Mizuki was starting to seem friendlier and less volatile
But seeing Yuiichiro just completely set him off
I thought you were working on them
Very diligently
And the result?
This is a marked improvement
You were supposed to keep close watch over them
But I did watch them, sir
This morning, Kimizuki attacked Hyakuya to test his ability
And maintain his alpha dominance over the students
And?
Did you step in and break up the fight?
Actually, I stayed in hiding and enjoyed the show
I'm beginning to think you're not very good at your job
Enough of this!
Uh, are they okay?
They'll be fine
Let's get to work, everyone
Maybe I can teach the rest of you something
Lieutenant Colonel Ichinose
I don't mean to intrude
But do you have time to talk?
No
And don't come in here without permission
I just have a question about the Cursed Gear aptitude test a week from now
On that day, I'll be given the chance to try out for the top-ranked Black Demon series, right?
You're starting to wear out your welcome
My grades are better than everyone else's
I'm the strongest student in class
Why is it so important for you to have that kind of power?
The army does background checks on all of us
I'm sure you've read the files on each potential recruit
Yeah, I know all about your history
You've got a sister who's been infected with the apocalypse virus
And now you're looking for a cure
I understand your intentions
There are certain perks that come with being a member of the Moon Demon Company
Things like unlimited medical treatments that are unavailable to the rest of the public
Unfortunately, you've still got a lot of training to go through
In your current state, you couldn't even touch the Cursed Gear
It would feed off of your desire for a cure and eventually consume you
But I bet that you're going to let Hyakuya try out any weapon he wants, aren't you?
That all remains to be seen
Although he has shown some talent
He's even broken free from a demon once already
And despite his attitude, he's someone who looks out for his friends
That's bullshit!
I'm way stronger than he'll ever be!
Strength isn't everything
You need to learn that
Make some friends
Form a support system
Stop taking everything on yourself
Otherwise...
When you find yourself face to face with a demon
You'll have no chance of controlling it
Demons feast upon desperation and rage
If you attempted a contract now, you'd be swallowed whole and never find your way out
Hey everyone!
Listen up students!
In preparation for next week's Cursed Gear Aptitude Test, I will be assessing all of your abilities
If you can't show me you're ready here, then you'll have to keep training and take the test at a later date
So do your best, okay?
That's a lot of pressure
Whatever happens, I'm gonna kick ass and prove that I'm the strongest here
Here we go again
Today I'll be evaluating you based on how well you work together with others
Go ahead, everyone choose a partner to work with
Huh?
What?
A partner?
Hey, Yoichi?
We're going to be the best team in the whole class, don't you agree?
Uh, yeah
What are you guys doing together?
What about me?
Hey!
Let's see
Is there anyone left?
Seriously?
Your attention, please!
Now that everyone has chosen a partner, it's time to put your game faces on
Let's get this party started!
So we're facing the army's cursed puppets
It looks like they're pretty damn slow
The faster we trash these things, the faster our scores go up
It's a problem!
Quit messing around, we both have to go after the same one
Yeah, I thought you were going to follow me!
That's negative points for them
They're not off to a very good start
Excuse me, I have an urgent message
Shit!
You have a sister?
Shut up, bastard.
Please keep training.
I apologize to everyone for the disruption.
Hey, what are you doing?
If your sister is dying,
you don't have time to stand around here apologizing.
Look, this doesn't concern you.
My goal is to impress everyone in this training exercise.
That's the only thing that matters.
Then you're abandoning your sister.
Shut up.
What gives you the right to weigh in on my personal life?
Getting recruited means everything.
Start up the puppets again.
How stupid can you be?
Family isn't something you can ignore.
If your sister were to die,
you'd always regret not being there when she needed you.
We're in the clear.
It looks like she's going to pull through for now,
but the equipment we have here isn't made to combat this virus.
I understand, Doc.
But soon, I'll be joining the Moon Demon Company.
Then I can transfer her over to the army facility.
Please, take care of her just a little while longer.
I'm glad that she ended up being okay.
Who'd have thought?
You walk around acting like a badass,
but it turns out you're doing it all for your sister.
You should have just told me about her.
That being said,
I'm still taking the strongest cursed gear for myself.
This is your fault.
I'm getting a bad evaluation because of you.
I won't be eligible to join the company.
Because of that,
my sister won't be saved.
Only a coward would give up on her life so easily.
Pick yourself up and start fighting for what you want.
That's what I'm going to do.
And nothing as small as a bad evaluation is going to stop me.
If I'm being honest,
I don't even need the Moon Demon Company.
I'd still fight all by myself.
But you're going to give up on your family just like that?
What?
Who said anything about giving up?
Damn it!
How did I end up stuck with you?
You're a nosy little prick.
But you are right about not giving up.
What's that?
Don't forget that you punched me
since I got to be with my sister.
I'm grateful you talked me into leaving the training room.
And I guess I owe you an apology
since you'll get a bad score on the evaluation too.
The only person with the right
to evaluate this fool is me.
Man, could you be any more annoying?
Today, we've gathered all nobles
with the progenitor's blood
to address a growing concern.
Humans!
The Japanese Imperial Demon Army
has been ramping up operations
and increasing their numbers
in northern Tokyo.
This human organization
is killing our brothers,
expanding its territory
and flirting with forbidden enchantments
to increase their power.
According to our intel,
they are once again experimenting
on the Seraph of the End.
If we allow these humans
to continue to rise and gain strength,
another plague like the one
that occurred eight years ago
will surely come to pass.
You needn't worry about that.
Because we're exterminating
the Japanese Imperial Demon Army.
We're going to war!
To ensure that we continue
to rule this world,
we'll have to slaughter
the greedy livestock resistance
once and for all!
Extermination.
The Seraph of the End.
Don't worry, you.
I'm coming to your rescue soon.
It was definitely true of coming to us.
I've been asking you help you to try the entire country.
But we're going to buy a ticket
and let's wrap it up.
I need your blood, you'll be in love tonight, I've got great light.
I need your blood, you'll be in love tonight, I'll be in love tonight, I'll be in love tonight, I'll be in love tonight.
I need your blood, you'll be in love tonight, I'll be in love tonight, I'll be in love tonight.
I need your blood, you'll be in love tonight.
Next time on Seraph of the End, Black Demon's Contract.